Good morning. It's Wednesday, February
25th. You're watching The Program with
Ted Rall and John Kiriakou. Good
morning, John.
>> Morning, Ted. Good to see you.
>> Good to see you, too. Okay, so let's get
to it. Obviously, um I don't know if you
stayed up and I did. I endured the State
of the Union last night. I'm It's It's
as exhausting as the administration and
the state of America itself.
>> And he proudly said beforehand this was
going to be the longest State in
American history and it was.
>> And it was.
>> In fact, New York Times sent out a push
notification
toward the end saying he's just passed
the record. It's the longest State of
the Union. Like that's supposed to mean
something.
>> I know. It's like that's not necessarily
a good thing. That's not Hank Aaron
hitting number 714.
So,
you see how So, we'll talk about the
State of the Union.
Victor Orban is is our main story today
or at least should we were thinking it
would be.
He put the kibosh on the EU's latest
cash infusion to to the Ukrainians as
well as more Russians more anti-Russian
sanctions. We'll talk about the veto
power that he has there in Hungary. And
and finally, also yesterday and I think
we have to talk about this with the
developments in Iran, Trump made a claim
not quite up to the WMDs in Iraq claim,
but he claimed that ICBMs
intercontinental ballistic missiles
could soon reach the United States from
Iran and that's not what the
intelligence community says.
So
>> simply not true.
>> So, we So, anyway, and of course, as
always, please like, follow, and share
the show. Robbie West, producer, is out
today taking care of his wife who is in
post-op and is recovering.
Things I things went about as well as
could be expected, I think.
But, we're all praying for her and so,
you know, we Also, if you feel like uh
throwing some a cash infusion their way,
that would not be a bad thing. I'll go
ahead and put the URL up there for
Robbie's GoFundMe. Um he'll be mad that
I did that. Sorry, Robbie. I don't care.
Okay. Now, um
let's
uh let's see, what other housekeeping do
we have to do? Okay, so we have some
questions and we can get into those um
or we can skip right into the State of
the Union. What do you want to do?
>> Yeah, let's jump into the State of the
Union.
>> Okay.
>> Um
let me ask you, Ted,
were you as frustrated with Democrats as
I was? I mean, we we knew we knew what
to expect from Donald Trump. We knew
that he was going to be angry and ugly
and mean-spirited. We knew he because
it's his nature and he did it on
purpose. He gets a kick out of it. But
the Democrats walked right into his
trap. Right into it.
>> Yeah. Well, he There were several traps.
So, the traps kept getting laid. Um you
know, the most notable one where he
obviously had coordinated this with the
Republican leadership where he said,
"Please, you know, but you know it's
trouble where it's like, you know, I'm
going to ask a question and if you uh
agree with it, stand up and if you
don't, stay sitting down." And it's
like, "Do you Do you think that the
priorities of uh you know,
elected officials should be to
prioritize the US citizens over illegal
immigrants?"
And uh and and so that's a trap and he
just let it lie there.
>> And and of course, John
Fetterman jumps right up.
>> Right.
>> The only Democrat.
>> That's right.
Now, the thing is, I happen to agree
with the answer to that question. It's a
It's a trap, of course. It is a trap,
but of course, obviously, the priority
of American elected officials should be
US citizens.
Goes without saying. But Democrats don't
know what to do in a situation like
that. They should be prepared to act as
one.
Um you know, maybe all get up and walk
out at that moment. Um but they There
should have been instead of just sitting
there like basically screwed.
John, I thought the Democrats
you know
one of my Republican friends
text me this morning and said oh you
know Donald Trump kicked ass. I don't
think Donald Trump kicked ass at all.
But he said but he said oh the Democrats
looked terrible. That's true too. The
Democrats did look terrible.
They just didn't know what to do John. I
mean they didn't even in in years past
they had their their lame little like
micro signs that they used to have a
sign up.
>> were wearing the tags release the
Epstein files.
>> Right like my news.
>> But how come you didn't wear those when
Biden was president?
>> Right good question. And also why are
they like two inches across?
You know you're on national television.
You know the only spiciness came from Al
Green.
You know.
>> Just Al Green.
>> And and like you know and I thought you
know the Democrats just didn't seem to
know what to do. They weren't willing to
be there was no civil disobedience here.
I mean you desperately needed at some
points when he was insulting them
questioning their patriotism and their
sanity calling them crazy. At some point
you need a you. And it's like
where is it? What are they so worried
about that they're the sergeant at arms
is going to kick them out? Whoop watch
it on TV later.
>> What a joke.
>> I mean
you know
first of all Al Green
Al Green did not impress me last night
with with his big sign. The the
Democratic leadership said no signs.
You're going to get thrown out. He pulls
out this giant sign black people are not
apes. Okay.
Great. And then you get thrown out. And
so what what have you accomplished?
>> But also if you get thrown out get
thrown out spicily. Struggle. Fight
back.
>> And he didn't. He just walked out.
>> up and went out. I mean it's all so
performative. And the American people
know that.
>> sides. Both sides. I I I hated it. And
I'll tell you what, when I was in
college, Reagan was president, the
country was divided, Democrats on one
side, Republicans on on the other. I
enjoyed those speeches.
I enjoyed them. They were substantive.
>> Mhm.
>> On both sides. You could agree to
disagree, you could stand up for what
you believed in, but there was still
decorum.
And there's no decorum on either side.
>> It's a clown show.
>> It is.
>> And I mean, like it literally was a you
know, the I thought it was like the the
announce I mean, I never thought I would
say that I would see a Congressional
Medal of Honor, which is the highest
award that member of the military can
receive from the civilian branch of
government. Um you know, it's basically
like the the the quad to gay or the
national to nail in France.
Like it was degraded by this spectacle.
>> It wasn't the Congressional Medal of
Honor, was it?
>> Yeah, it was.
>> it was a Presidential Medal of Freedom.
>> No. No, no, no. It's the Congressional
Medal of Honor. I looked it up. It's the
with the blue ribbon. And like Melania
blue ribbon.
>> Melania gave gave the Congressional
Medal of Honor to that World War Korea
veteran.
>> brain didn't allow me to realize that
that was the Congressional Medal of
Honor.
>> It was and it was like I I expected
Montel Williams to step out any moment
or Jerry Springer. There's like but
wait, there's more. We not the hockey
team I'm like, okay, whatever. Um I
thought that the You're right.
>> Oh my god, the Congressional Medal of
Honor. Oh my god.
>> debased. That is a an august like every
soldier dreams maybe of being considered
for that. Um it's like then the I mean
and you know, 99.999%
will never see one much less have one. I
mean, it's it was debased. It was
depraved. Um the
the the
the the reuniting of the Venezuelan
political dissident who had been
recently freed, the father, with his
daughter. It's like, but wait, GUESS
WHAT'S BEHIND DOOR NUMBER TWO. I mean,
it wasn't Donald Trump is a consummate
entertainer, but it really felt like the
WWE more than ever before.
It was but I thought John, to me
this moment was particularly repugnant
and and made me ashamed to be American
was when he you saw the look on John
Roberts' face when he first came in and
you knew this was like
he he's a smart man, he knows what's
coming, he knows he's going to be
insulted and humiliated on national
television and yet he's there, right?
It's it's horrible. It's like the kind
of Saddam Hussein used to do and
then
he he he it happens. He
insults the Supreme Court, questions
their decisions, which he's already
ignored, says he's going to continue to
ignore the Supreme Court. Four of their
four or five members are right there.
Barrett, Justice Barrett, like looked
looked you the look on her face, he
appointed her. The look on her face was
priceless. She had this look of like, oh
my god.
>> You know, interestingly, I'm sorry to
interrupt you.
Interestingly,
the Trump appointees to the Supreme
Court
have been pretty good.
>> That's true.
>> They've been surprisingly good. It's
these dinosaurs like Alito and Thomas
appointed by the moderate presidents
that are just disasters.
>> No, that's that's been that is
interesting, John. Thank you for that
observation. Uh
But I thought I mean, do you make do you
think this is important as I do? I mean,
because I've never I don't I've never
seen
>> In my opinion, they should have gotten
up and left.
>> have. We've never had a president
that has
vocalized the words
I'm going to ignore the Supreme Court.
>> No.
>> Never.
>> And and and not especially not in such a
high-profile setting.
>> Yeah. It's a
It's a direct constitutional challenge.
>> It is a direct constitutional challenge,
and I thought it was appalling. And I
thought that the um you know, there was
just no resistance at all worth noting.
>> You know what?
Matina Matina makes a good point here.
It could have been worse.
Boring and lies is better than we're
going to war. And and there was talk
>> are going to war.
>> There was talk about that beforehand.
Like, was he actually You said it, Ted,
as well.
Was he going to use the uh the speech to
announce that we were in the midst of an
attack on Iran?
>> I'm sure the Iranians were expecting
that. And we'll talk about Iran, and
obviously
>> My glasses off, huh?
>> John, I I got to say I I also think
politically domestically um Donald Trump
really squandered an opportunity
yesterday. I mean, the Republicans are
up against the are really on the ropes
um in going into the midterms.
>> And he didn't lay out any plan for them.
>> No plan. He didn't help them at all. If
you're If you're a you know, if you're
an incumbent Republican, you're you're
very worried this morning. Um
and uh you know, his polls are in the
toilet. I mean, at 37% a president might
credibly be thinking about resigning,
not delivering a State of the Union
address. Um and that number seems to
have not found its floor yet. We may It
may continue to drop. Who knows? It
might stay steady or even go up, but
right now but
he committed the Joe Biden mistake.
Don't don't don't believe your lying
bank account. The economy is roaring.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Roaring.
>> Yes, he did. [clears throat]
>> People don't like that.
>> Yeah. They don't. I agree with you.
>> and I I think it's like it's not
specifically really about this
particular speech that's going to change
minds, but if that but that is the
messaging of the of the administration
and the Republican Party and people are
going to hear that day after day and
what that introduces is hopelessness.
Right? I mean, literally everything that
he announced was stuff that, you know,
basically look at what we did. Now, we
all know about health care. We know that
the health care Trump RX thing is lame.
We know that the Trump savings accounts
are lame. Um, you know, the American
people don't think that help is on the
way.
>> [clears throat]
>> If you're suffering, you need to either
know that help is on the way or help
might be on the way. They don't feel
like that now.
>> I think you're right.
Yeah, I think you're right. But I want
to reiterate something that we just
said. There was no plan.
And this was essentially the only
nationally televised opportunity
between now and November
to lay out a plan that the Republicans
can run on as a party.
>> Mhm.
>> You know, and watching Mike Johnson sit
behind uh
Trump and just smile and nod his head
and clap, it's like, buddy,
this is on you.
You should be leading your caucus and
you're not. You're just sitting there
praying that that Jesus, you know,
delivers the best ideas to you. How's
that working out?
>> [laughter]
>> I mean, if I were Mike Johnson, I'd have
Newt Gingrich living on my couch and I'd
be asking him every morning, noon, and
night how he pulled off 1994 by
nationalizing the midterms. Um, you
know, that's that's what the Republicans
should be doing and they should have a
a real plan for the workplace, a real
plan for AI, a real plan for healthcare.
Lord knows they've had 10 years to come
up with one on healthcare. Um
and they just
I don't know if they can. I don't know
if their donors won't allow them to. I
don't really, you know, I don't know if
they're too disorganized. I don't know
if this president's too scattered.
All of the above, probably. Some other
stuff I'm not thinking of. But it was I
mean, you know, we we knew it was going
to be like that. That's why I didn't
bother to make the State of the Union,
you know, when I who came up with the
with the headline for today, the main
story, cuz I knew it wouldn't be the
main story.
>> Yeah.
>> But it's still
I mean, it's still even though you know
it's coming, it's still depressing.
>> Still, I want to crack on the Democrats
because they are utterly devoid of any
ideas.
>> That's true.
>> terrible. And if if anything came out of
last night,
it is the absolute necessity, the
immediate necessity for viable third
parties.
>> Right, but that's not going to happen.
At least not on the national stage.
>> Nope.
It's not.
>> It's got to be, you know, really truly I
think the the model is like the
the Farmer-Labor Party or all these
early 20th century parties, right? Like
>> the uh like the Socialist Party and so
on. You got to develop regional
strength. You've got to get some
I mean, look at Bernie Sanders, right?
He's the closest thing to a resistance
that we have.
>> Yes.
>> was an independent
for uh for for for mayor of Burlington,
Vermont. That's where he started.
>> Yes.
>> And it took a long time for him he it
took, you know, decades before he
percolated up to the national stage, but
he did. That's what you have to do. It
That's the hard work. The left in this
country doesn't want to do the hard
work. They want to have a rally, you
know, on a beautiful Sunday every 4
months. That's it. They don't want to
stand out in the rain every day. Uh you
know, and and they don't want to
build a third party from the grassroots.
They don't want to organize the working
class. They should they don't they want
to have a national strike just like
that, you know, you buy through Facebook
groups.
And again,
vote for me cuz I'm not the other guy is
not a strategy.
>> No.
>> Although it can be it it works
sometimes, but then like but then you
but this is the problem.
You know, you look at the likes of
Chuck Schumer looked like he was not
just already dead but dead and halfway
rotten.
>> [laughter]
>> He was he looked like a like a
scarecrow. Like he was he was kind of
like
he was hanging like this. Like
>> Yeah, exactly. So so sure, let's say
Trump is unpopular. The Republican at
least the Republican house is unpopular
and so the Democrats win 15, 20, 25,
whatever seats.
And then what? They've got no no ideas.
How in the world do they intend to
govern?
>> Well, they'll have
>> And and I'll tell you another thing.
If the Democrats do win a majority in
the house and then they immediately move
to impeach Trump again,
>> Mhm.
>> they should never win another race.
>> That's what they will do.
>> As punishment, they should never win
another race.
>> No, they're they're utterly worthless.
Um, you know, they're just they they're
not they're completely incapable of
rising to the occasion and like even the
fact that like the boycott like Hakeem
Jeffries and and Chuck Schumer told
their their you know, their caucuses,
um, don't you know, hey, you can boycott
or or not.
Look, you got to all be on the same page
as a party. Either you all show up
>> Yes.
>> and you all do the same thing or you all
don't show up. Which would have been
very powerful, too.
>> That's right. It would have
>> they would have filled the seats anyway,
but
>> Yes. They would have. You know, it's
funny. CNN was talking beforehand about
uh
about the seats.
And I didn't realize what Of course,
there are way fewer seats than what they
need. And so, um
I didn't realize that people go there
6 hours in advance to stake out a seat.
And they'll bring like lunch and dinner
with them.
And just hold their food on their lap.
And the Democrats like 112 Democrats
didn't show up yesterday. Between
House members and senators.
And that's why they were able to to fill
all those seats with
the Supreme Court, the cabinet,
visitors, even the sub cabinet, all
kinds of stuff.
It's just not the way it used to be. at
all.
>> Elliot Covered has a question for you,
John pertinent to all this. Did you
notice that that disgusting slob John
Fetterman actually wore a suit last
night like a normal human being?
>> First thought in my mind, like I can't
believe that idiot finally put on a
suit.
Finally.
Cuz if he feels so strongly about his
about his cheap ass hoodie and stuff,
wear the hoodie. Hypocrite.
>> Yeah, exactly. But he didn't This was
the big one, right? So, John, I heard
you say that Necco Wafers weren't around
in Lincoln's time, but on the Necco
Wafer package it says 1847.
>> 1847.
I read that it was 1878 and uh yeah,
somebody else corrected me on that.
Yeah.
>> Um let's see.
>> it had to do with the recipe of the
Necco Wafers. There was something about
it being a Necco Wafer.
>> No A Guy Speaking, John, did not forward
my your essay about immigration. John,
please do that. Okay.
>> I'll say it again.
>> Did you're supposed to forward me um A
Guy Speaking's essay about immigration?
Or if you did, I didn't see it.
>> Oh oh oh oh yes. Yes, I have it. I'll
send it to you. Yes.
>> Okay. All right.
Uh
Ted Pink He's uh Pink Lady wants to
know, "Please ask my question from the
past 2 days. John, thank you for asking
it again. John, do you still consider
yourself to have sociopathic traits?
You seem so empathetic and kind today.
By the way, I hope I get my stud muffin
photo in the mail."
>> [laughter]
>> Um you know, what that what that
sociopathic tendency was
was
a willingness to
break the law or to work in
moral, legal, and ethical gray areas.
So, I'd have to say yes.
If
if
I were still in the CIA and I had I was
instructed to break into a house and
plant a listening device, yeah, sure. Of
course, I would.
No, a normal person wouldn't do that.
>> Yeah, by the way, being a sociopath
doesn't mean that you're not kind.
>> Well, and a non-sociopath.
>> Right, but I'm just saying
>> about sociopathic tendencies.
>> Right, and I'm also saying but also it's
like I think it's a misnomer people
think sociopaths are necessarily mean.
They're
they're uh rude or whatever. That's
That's That's not the profile at all. Uh
Fraz Mattaz, um Laith Marouf said on
Nemesis Show
uh that re that unified command for
CENTCOM was moved to the big base on
Crete as Mossad HQ allegedly got hit in
Tel Aviv last time. Is that a target?
>> Interesting.
We have a gigantic naval presence in
Crete, gigantic. So, that would actually
make sense. I didn't see that, and that
did not appear in the Greek press, by
the way.
You know what? I'm going to call it call
it up right now. Maybe I missed it.
Uh no.
>> Um Keenan Keenan Bailey, do we Do we
have the chance to think about the
implications on NATO if Israel and
Turkey were to engage in a kinetic
conflict? I think this was a question
from last week you were asking. Well, we
actually did come back to it, but and we
said that yeah, it could be the end of
NATO.
>> Yeah, that's that's worth
writing about.
>> It is.
Yeah.
>> I think that is just such a great
question and
>> That's a Kuriakou. That's a classic
Kuriakou essay.
>> It it it is.
>> You should do it.
>> to jump on that.
>> Yeah, you do that. Um I'm my already
have my topic for this week, which is uh
if you know, what are the chances of the
Republicans canceling the midterms? Um
Elliot, I went to bed before Spanberger
gave the response. She's so generic and
boring, a real DNCIA
Democrat. Um so, one of my problems with
the Democratic response, which I did not
watch, John, is they the way they they
they write it in advance, right? It's
it's a speech before she's seen the
president's speech, she's already
written it and and she just reads it.
>> That's not a response.
>> No, it's not a response.
>> That's just a I don't know.
>> It's a campaign speech.
>> Yeah, it's a yeah, it's stupid. I mean,
really truly, um the response should be
someone taking notes throughout the
throughout the speech and then saying,
"Okay, when Trump said this, actually
that." Right? They don't do that. That's
why I didn't watch.
>> No, she's she's terrible. You know, she
she's a moderate Democrat.
Uh
which in my mind and all my friends from
my hometown that I'm on Facebook with,
they're all going to
just flip out that I'm saying this. But
to me, she's a conservative Democrat.
>> Oh, for sure.
>> very much a DNC, like a down the line
DNC, center of the road,
you know, don't want to offend the right
kind of person. And um
I I think she's
Look, in Virginia, our governors are
only allowed to serve one term. And so,
the minute they take the oath of office,
they're lame ducks. That's it. It's the
end of it. So, she'll she'll govern as
much as a governor can govern Virginia.
The state essentially runs itself.
And uh
she's already running for vice
president.
That's what this is all about. That's
why they made her
the uh the Democratic responder last
night.
>> with that.
>> She's begun her campaign for vice
president.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I mean, in a way though, I'm
glad that they didn't make a progressive
go and do the deliver the response
because they're not in charge of the
Democratic policy anyway. So, why do you
why should they have to go and
articulate
>> right.
>> Uh Nick Riviera, PhD, best part was when
he spoke about Somali pirates and the
camera pans to Ilhan Omar.
Maybe the best I don't know.
>> Hi, Dr. Dick.
>> Yeah.
>> First of all,
>> It was very funny.
>> But yeah, that
I
See, this was another thing that
bothered me. Like, did he really need to
attack the squad? That was just
gratuitous and unnecessary. But then,
when the Republicans started chanting
USA, USA,
>> God, which they always do.
>> Ilhan Omar and uh what's what's her
name? The um
the uh Palestinian one. Um
Anyway,
>> Uh Rashida Tlaib.
>> Yeah, yeah, thank you.
Should not have started to chant KKK,
KKK. The country is not like the KKK.
No, it's not. And that was offensive.
See, this is what I mean. Like, decorum
is just collapsed on Capitol Hill.
We thought things were bad in the '80s
or in the '90s even with with Bill
Clinton on the one side and uh
and Newt Gingrich on the other, it's
worse now. Like, everybody's just
classless.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, by the way, it's
true what ugly stupid loser says, there
were two Medals of Honor.
>> Yeah, the old man got one.
>> Mhm.
>> And the kid got one from Venezuela. Two
Congressional Medals of Honor. Just
absolutely astounding to me. I mean,
there were guys who,
you know, gave up their lives in
Afghanistan while mowing down a dozen
Taliban and saving everybody in their
platoon, and they got the Silver Star.
So, I I don't understand how these
things
>> I Well, look, and I don't understand I
mean, I guess it's like I understand how
the words um Alex Pretty and Renee could
didn't get uttered, but it was also I
think a squandered opportunity.
Um you know, I mean, look, the thing is
um
even moderate analysts this morning are
saying that Trump basically set out to
to solidify his base, and that's what
was important, and he and he got that
done. I'm not sure I agree with that.
>> I I don't agree. Um and Jake Tapper
talked about this last night.
He said that
that 8 months ago Trump was pulling 90%
among Republicans and 46% among
independents. Now, he's 82% among
Republicans and 26% among independents.
So, if you're trying to win back that 8%
of Republicans and shore up your base,
all you're going to do is alienate more
independents.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, look, I think that
I'm a big proponent generally of a base
strategy, but I think at this point
Trump is underwater even with his base
on the issues that they liked him about,
immigration and the economy. Um and
that's not, you know, I mean, he doesn't
have those anymore. He lost credibility
because of the way that the deportations
have been implemented. No question, he
sealed the border. Although, frankly,
to be fair, Joe Biden, outgoing Joe
Biden, sealed the border
uh a couple of weeks before he dropped
out of the race, right? Trying to save
himself. And then, it stayed sealed, and
Trump just kept it sealed. Um you know,
I mean, Trump definitely gets his gets
that credit, but still
>> I have a good friend who is a
an investigative journalist, and she
went down to Eagle Pass, Texas.
She called me from Eagle Pass. She was
standing on a hill overlooking the
border, and she said, "Never in my life
have I actually seen a border that's
open."
She said, "People were just streaming
across it." And the
the
ICE guys or Border Patrol or Border
Protection, whatever they call
themselves today, they were just
standing there overwhelmed.
The border was just open, and people
were coming across.
>> Yeah, uh streaming in. I mean, I I will
say I have seen that in, you know,
Central Asia and places like
>> Oh, I I I saw that in Somalia.
>> I saw that between Uzbekistan and
Kazakhstan.
>> in Texas.
>> Uh no, it's Well, look, it was left
open. I mean, and that's insane. Uh
Desert Fox 41, question for both of us,
what do we make of the track to war with
Iran? By all reports, it was supposed to
start this past weekend.
I'm not so sure about that. I think
they're still trying to
Trump thinks he's still negotiating, um
sort of.
And uh
you know,
it's I mean, I think the the thing is
from the US military perspective, the
longer they wait, the better, cuz
they'll have more assets in place and
it's easier.
>> I I apologize to about changing the
subject, but
>> Ah, be my guest.
>> But is it rational says, "Can we talk
about Texas representative of Tony
Gonzales?"
>> Oh, yeah.
>> He talked a staff member, a married
staff member, into having an affair,
into sending nudes.
She became so
distraught, so depressed that she set
herself on fire.
>> Right. Right?
>> And died.
>> Mhm.
>> And he refuses to resign.
>> [snorts]
>> Now, finally, there are Republicans
calling for him to resign. The the the
uh
primary is I think Saturday and he's got
very strong opposition from the right
within the primary. But this son of a
refuses to resign. And and he
denied and denied and denied and then
the staffer's husband released the text
messages and he's like, "Okay, well, all
right. Yeah, I guess I did it."
What do you think of this clown?
He should be prosecuted for manslaughter
or depraved indifference. And I get that
depraved indifference is a misdemeanor.
I get it. But you can still get a year
in in prison.
>> Well, is that a law in Texas is the
question.
>> Well, that's a good question. I don't
know.
>> Um
>> I don't know.
>> It seems like depraved indifference is
part of Texas's state culture. Um
I yeah, I mean
I got to say cynically, if I were
advising him, I would say stay put
in this news environment, everyone's
going to forget all about you, the
headlines are going to move on, don't
feed the fire, you can you can hang on
and no one's going to everyone's going
to forget all about it. Just don't say
[clears throat] anything about it. I
mean, I'm being cynical, but I think
honestly, he can ride this out.
>> God, I can't I can't even believe it.
>> I mean, I'm not saying he should, I'm
just saying, you know, he can.
>> You know, to tell you the truth, if I
were the husband, I would stomp him
until his brain was pudding. I really
would.
>> Well, you might also be pissed at your
wife, [laughter] though.
I mean, you know.
>> Oh my god.
>> she had she had she had free will,
right?
>> Yeah, she had free will. See, but this
is
>> adult.
>> This is my This is my nature and I've
taken over this over the years, but
for whatever reason, I always blame the
guy, the other guy.
>> Yeah, I don't I'm not like that.
>> my experience that yeah.
>> No, I mean, that's like
>> came in and ruined my family and it's
like, "No, no, no. No, no. That's not
exactly right."
>> Yeah, well, obviously, I'm I'm on the
team who would disagree with give you
for that, John. I disagree with
that. I mean, you you know it's wrong.
But But there's the emotional response
and then there's the logical response.
>> That's right.
>> Um you know, I always feel like it's the
opposite. Like um you know, if you like
the person who made like
you know, she made the oath to her
husband, not that guy not the
congressman, right?
>> Right. Right.
>> So,
you know, they he didn't know her
anything he didn't owe him anything.
Anyway, um only one ham question for
both of us. Do we Do we happen to enjoy
any sports?
What's your favorite to watch live?
John, you better answer this cuz my
question is short. The end. My answer is
no.
>> I do. I love I love
baseball and football. I watch both
regularly. And then football is like
such a big deal to me that even if the
game's on here at home, I'll walk to a
Steelers bar in Clarendon, Arlington,
Virginia here, and um just so I can be
surrounded by 500 screaming Pittsburgh
Steelers fans.
>> I I'm jealous of people who have that
kind of passion. Uh I was a baseball fan
as a kid. If buskashi were available to
watch here, I would go every day. Um
that that's my favorite sport. But
unfortunately, you have to go to
Afghanistan or Central Asia to see that.
>> You do, and it's weird.
>> It's amazing, though. Um
it's so cool.
Uh I love this question. John Margery,
uh good morning, guys. Question, if you
could replace Trump with another world
leader, who would you choose?
>> Oh, that's an easy one for me.
Konstantine Mitsotakis. This guy has
proven to be such a terrific leader for
Greece. I will admit that I did not vote
for him the first time. Uh but I have
been very pleasantly surprised. And when
he came to the United States during
Trump's first term to meet with Trump,
the Washington Post commented that his
English was better than Trump's.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah, he's got a bachelor's degree and a
master's degree from Harvard and a PhD
from Oxford. And he's been a terrific
prime minister.
>> I don't have one because I would have to
pull from the past. To be honest, I
would have gone for Hugo Chavez or
>> What?
>> Yeah, someone like that. I mean, I love
the fact that like Hugo Chavez
nationalized all the golf courses and
turned them into into public parks. Um
he the way he trolled the rich and uh
nationalized uh you know,
uh you know, public assets for the
benefit of the public. Someone like
that.
I mean, I think we need like a radical
lefty who's going to like mix up cuz
we've never had one. We've had radical
right-wingers. We've got one right now.
But um you know,
I it's like I don't know as a permanent
choice, but sort of
someone like that. I know that's a crazy
choice.
>> [laughter]
>> But um
>> Yeah.
>> Um John Kavanaugh is a menace. This is
from Malarkey. And overrode treaties
with indigenous people
and is allowing fourth amendment
>> not saying I'm not saying that I would
want to the guy to be my, you know,
housemate or anything. I'm just saying
he's not Clarence Thomas or Sam Alito.
>> Ha. Kevin Cronin says, "John, I'm
straight, but I got to say you look
marvelous without glasses."
>> Thank you. I wish I could see, but I'm
blind. Just blind without glasses.
>> Um
let's see.
Uh
NPR says the hockey OH, YEAH, THE HOCKEY
PLAYER.
That's right. The hockey player got the
Presidential Medal of Freedom.
They gave it the Presidential Medal of
Freedom to the hockey player.
>> The goalie.
>> Who by the way, was chewing his cud the
entire time. I don't know if he was
chewing tobacco or gum or his his cud or
whatever the it was, but he's there
like
like an old man with chom- sucking on
his dentures. Did you notice that?
>> I did.
>> He was on national television. It's like
>> You know, I remember when
>> pig rotten pig are you?
>> When I was a little kid when I was a
little kid, right after the Beatles
broke up, John Lennon was on the Tonight
Show and I was up for some reason. I was
sitting on my mom's lap and John John
Lennon was chewing gum
while he was giving his interview to
Johnny Carson. And my mom says, "Who
does he think he is chewing gum like a
cow chews its cud? Shame on him. He goes
on national TV and chews gum."
>> [laughter]
>> I remember that.
>> Yeah.
New American says, "Raul's you
recommendation is painfully ridiculous,
childish and unhelpful."
Yeah, probably, but I don't know if it's
unhelpful. I mean, look, I I wanted the
Democrats to show some sign of life. Um
and you know, when you you're being
degraded and humiliated and, you know,
treated disrespectfully, not just
disagreed with vehemently,
you know, it calls for some sort of
violent response, you know?
>> [snorts]
>> God forbid.
>> You know, I mean, if someone were
talking to me like that in a bar, I'd
punch them in the face.
>> Yeah, seriously.
Yeah.
>> Um
What's left about the Democratic Party?
Trouble wants to know.
>> Agreed.
>> Miriam Adelson got a Medal of Freedom.
That's true. That's true. She actually
purchased one
with her hundreds of millions of dollars
to the Trump campaign and the RNC.
>> LoggerJogger, any thoughts on Anthropic
snubbing the Department of Defense, not
allowing them to use their AI tech to
make super intelligent bombs?
If the war machine wants it, won't they
just take it?
>> And that's exactly what uh
what Pete Hegseth said yesterday.
>> [snorts]
>> If you don't give it to us, we're just
going to take it.
>> How can they do that?
>> I don't think that they can.
>> Nah, I mean what
>> I suppose, you know, maybe you could
make an argument in wartime
>> Right.
>> take a a company's IP and just say, "Oh,
we want it."
>> Nah.
Totally. Totally.
>> Yeah.
>> Um Desert Fox, what do you make of the
Knights of Columbus being in Ukraine? I
got an email, had no idea they had a
role there.
First I've heard of it. Do you know?
>> Yeah, I
I That's the first I've heard of it, but
I I think it doesn't really surprise me.
Ukraine is pretty much, you know, half
Orthodox and half Catholic and
the Knights of Columbus, I guess, think
that they have a role. I wouldn't be
surprised.
>> [snorts]
>> Um John um redacted wants to know, "What
are the details on your University of
Pittsburgh speech in March? I live
nearby and would like to attend."
>> Oh, thank you. You know, it is
tentatively
on March 11th. I'm going to I'm going to
ping the professor today.
Uh actually, maybe I have it here in
front of me.
No, I don't have it.
It's tentatively the 11th of March, but
I'll say something in advance. Thanks
for asking.
>> Uh Bettina, did you hear the sailors are
putting their clothes in the toilets to
back them up so they can leave as they
wait for war with Iran?
>> There was a piece
on
Fox, I think it was, day before
yesterday about the USS Gerald Ford
having such a significant plumbing
problem where there's human like up
to your ankles, literally. That the only
thing they can do to take care of it is
to turn around and go back to Norfolk.
And I wondered when when this came out 2
days ago if it was sabotage.
>> Sabotage. It sounds like it.
>> Sure seems like it.
>> Yeah, it sure sounds like it. Um
Who know who Nemarin, John Ted, do you
support Kurdish independence? If you
were advising, what would Kurds do to
achieve it? I 100% support Kurdish
independence.
>> 100%.
>> They were they are a distinct
nationality. They've earned it. They're
a distinct culture. Um they were
promised it in 1919 and the great powers
ignored them at the
during the uh signing of the Treaty of
Versailles.
So, um and what what should they do to
get it?
Well, I hate to say it, you have to
declare independence and uh
you know, you have to be willing to
fight for it, but the Kurds are good at
that. So,
you know, I mean, you're going to lose
lives is the problem.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> What do you think, John? Would you would
you advise them to do that?
>> Uh you know, I think that at least in
Iraq, the situation that they have now
is acceptable to them in that they have
autonomy and uh they have some control
over the northern oil fields,
but I I still I still support I've
always supported Kurdish independence
and it should be a a
an inclusive Kurdish independence and
when I say inclusive, I mean including
the Syrian Kurds, the Turkish Kurds, the
Iranian Kurds.
>> Uh Tammy wants to know, my fellow
Daytonian, uh what does Fetterman stand
for?
Israel.
>> Israel. That's it.
That's all. I mean, he was supposed to
stand for organized labor. I'm still
waiting for for that to show itself.
>> [snorts]
>> By the way, I do think that the uh
Democrats should have had signs with uh
Rene Goods and uh
Al- Alex uh Brady's faces on them.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, that would have been more
powerful.
>> Let's see. Uh
Is it practical to have a war when the
are full?
>> I know, right?
>> No.
>> Um
logistics are important.
Uh
>> You know, and some of those
some of those ships, I've been on a
bunch of them over the years, they're so
overcrowded. You have to hot bunk. Like
in in um submarines, for example, you
have hot bunks. So, you have three times
as many people as there are beds.
And everybody gets 8 hours in the bed.
And you you share the bed with two other
guys, you share the pillow with two
other guys. It's gross.
>> Yeah.
>> But there's just no space.
You know, and you have you have
thousands of cans of of canned food
that you walk [clears throat] on.
And you just eat the canned food as you
need it.
So, you're you're, you know, several
inches higher than you normally would
because you're walking on canned food
everywhere you go.
And the the only reason, especially with
nuclear subs, the only reason they come
up out of the water is to keep people
from going insane. They can stay
underwater for 6 months. But people lose
their minds.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it takes a certain
psychology. Brass Mat Hat says um he
wouldn't really blame
the wife
at the at the text. It seems like she
was coerced. Um he also used a position
of power as an elected official. Um you
know, that's fair. You know, that
reminds me of this this whole episode
reminded me of a story my mother told
me. So, my mother worked at NATO
headquarters in Paris in the late '50s,
early '60s. And um she heard she used to
um take night night shift subbing in for
her friend who was like switchboard
Susan. You know, night shift like uh you
know, connecting calls and on one of
those old-fashioned boards.
>> My mom did that.
>> And she was bored. And like she'd listen
to the calls. It was the middle of the
night and she had nothing to do. You
weren't allowed to read or anything. So
she'd listen to the calls. And Vice
President uh Lyndon B. Johnson was
staying at NATO headquarters in one of
the uh one of the the guest suites and
she heard him call a secretary and
basically coerce her to come him.
Um like and she she was like he was like
basically like threatening her and you
know from what my mom gathered he she
ultimately you know
caved in and had to go do it. So it does
happen.
>> Scandalous.
>> Yeah.
>> What a shame.
>> I mean it's not surprising though,
[laughter] right? I mean it's like not
LBJ.
>> will say though you know
at at the back end of all that
it's it's good to know the true
character of the person you're married
to. And so
>> That's true.
>> You know.
Better off now than then.
>> Well, that's true.
Um hey this is from Herman. Do we think
Ukraine will lose their entire country
or just parts? I think many of us have
been unimpressed with what Russia has
managed.
>> I don't think they'll lose their entire
country.
>> No, there's no. I think they're going to
lose roughly 20%.
>> I I totally agree with with that number.
Yeah. It's going to be what we said it
was going to be 5 years ago.
>> Mhm.
Um Pras Maters how about Fidel, Ted?
That would be interesting. Yes, I like I
like Fidel. Um although he would God
talk about long-winded.
>> He had 6 hour speeches.
>> God, he never stopped talking that guy.
Um John, did you know that your image is
being used as clickbait on YouTube? I
saw something this morning.
>> Yes, indeed.
>> Really?
>> Um I'm going to have a a major
announcement coming in the next few
days.
Uh
and I'm not going to be alone in
confronting some of these um
And you know what? I'm not going to say
anything. I'm going to have a big, very
positive announcement coming in the next
few days.
>> Positive is good. Um
Oh, and by the way, thanks for the two
bucks, uh DJ. Much
uh
>> [sighs]
>> Uh pa pa pa pa pa pa
>> Hey, uh
we're not hawking any coffee today, huh?
>> Oh, you know what? That is [laughter]
That's a That is like not true. That
can't be true. And in fact, here we go.
Let's Let's Let's do that.
Thank you for the reminder.
I'm just not as good without Robbie.
So, [clears throat] um still haven't
tried 1775 Coffee? Now's your shot. The
1775 Starter Kit just dropped. Only
1,000 units. You're getting the bold
dark roast that hits hard, the smooth
medium roast, and the Vitality Mushroom
Coffee for clean energy and laser focus.
No crash. All single origin, small
batch, toxin-free, and mold-free. Plus,
you're also getting a gold spoon clip
because freedom isn't scooped with
plastic, a frother strong enough to stir
up your coffee and your mother-in-law's
opinions, and a black 1775 Tumbler. It's
$170 worth of coffee and gear. Yours for
99. This is for the ones who've been
watching 1775 blow up on Rumble,
wondering if it's actually worth it.
Spoiler, it is. Go to
1775coffee.com/studio
and grab your starter kit before they're
gone. Bold beans, clean fuel, and a
morning routine that stands for
something, just like Rumble does. And
you'll be drinking the coffee that gets
Robbie West up two full hours earlier
than we do for to do this show.
Okay.
>> Very good.
>> Thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> I will say
>> Inside joke there.
>> I'm not uh
I'm not a fan of this mushroom coffee,
but my my partner drinks it and she
loves it.
>> I love mushrooms, but I don't like
mushrooms. But I don't like mushroom
coffee.
>> I just love coffee. I love the the taste
that I love just you know, one of the
things about about Starbucks and I I got
this from the book Starbucked which is a
it's it was a a number one best seller
from 20 years ago. It's a historical
document. Love the book. But
Starbucks roasts its coffee to within 5
seconds of it turning to ash.
And I freaking love the taste. I just
love it. I mean every morning I I make a
quadruple.
You know, a quadruple
mocha.
>> 22 Mike Mike. John, as you have a
speaking engagement in Vietnam coming
up, would you like to shed some light on
it? Um also, any thoughts about former
CIA officer Frank Snepp who wrote the
decent interval
>> Yeah, Frank Snepp Afghanistan.
>> Frank Snepp was a giant. He was one of
the one of the great analysts of his
generation. He was practically the first
one to call Vietnam the way it really
was and uh and that we were losing there
and that we were committing atrocities.
He paid for it with his career.
Brilliant author. He had to fight the
CIA's publications review board
practically to the end of his life.
Deep respect for Frank Snepp.
Um the speech in Vietnam
is going to be on the morning of the
10th of August. I'm I'm represented
right now by a speakers bureau in New
York called Gotham Artists and they
booked this speech for me to give to 300
Australian investment bankers
at their annual convention.
And my brother-in-law is so excited
that he's going to go with me.
We're going to We're going to meet in
Washington. We're going to fly to uh
South to to Vietnam through South Korea.
And um
and take a couple of extra days for
ourselves. I've never been to Vietnam.
I've always wanted to go. And uh I think
this is going to be a blast.
>> Are you going to Do you have anything on
your on your list? Like are you going to
Hanoi Hilton or
the tunnels?
>> Yes and yes. Yes to both. I only regret
that I don't have more than you know 5
days because otherwise I'd have a bunch
of suits custom made too. You can get
them custom made for 100 bucks a piece.
And uh
>> Oh, like in Hong Kong.
>> Yeah, just like in Hong Kong. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Although I
I don't find my You You're in more need
of suits these days than I am.
>> Yeah, I think so. I think I am.
>> Yeah. Or you could be Or you could just
you know, put on your hoodie.
Um Daddy of Triplets, thoughts from both
as as
are we as a country so far
to the left and right that a John Kasich
type of candidate, remember him, has no
chance? I'm stuck in the middle
with what seems like no representation.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
>> I think Yeah. I mean, I'm not going to
get into you know, my personal feelings
about you know, where things ought to
be. But yeah, no, I don't think there's
any place in the current political
environment for that kind of you know,
one from column A one from column B type
candidate anymore.
>> Yes. Agreed.
>> Uh you know, the the It's But the thing
is I kind of would take issue with left
versus right. It's Democrat versus
Republican is what we have going on and
it's about teams. You know, what's our
favorite sport? It's politics. And
people follow They love their team. It's
not about It's really not about anything
else.
>> Yeah.
Somebody just called John Fetterman
fetid
fetidman. [laughter]
Frasmentaz did. I love that. I wish I
had thought of that.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh train 9517.
Ted, I'd be interested in hearing about
a time in your career when you faced
significant challenges or found yourself
in a difficult situation. How did that
experience shape your worldview? Well,
we don't have a lot of time here. Um you
know, at some point um I would recommend
that you go listen to
I think we have it on YouTube um also
the uh Ted Rall A Life. You could you
know, one of the whole hours is about my
lawsuit with the LA Times. That was such
a moment and there have been
others professionally. Um I was sued by
Blockbuster Video um in the in the in
the '90s for doing a cartoon that
accused their CEO of being a right-wing
Christian nutcase, which was fair
because he was a right right-wing
Christian nutcase. Um but it was very
stressful. I had I was very poor. I was
just starting out as a syndicated
cartoonist. I was making like 400 bucks
a month um for San Francisco Chronicle
features. And
you know, the next thing you know, I've
been slapped with a $10 million
lawsuit in New York court in and I had
to it was horrible. And I have like you
know, TV vans parked in front of my
shitty little walk-up apartment in
Hell's Kitchen. Um and
>> this is terrible.
>> It was it was rough. But I mean it you
know, and so basically it was kind of
like
I have I was working at the time I had a
day job working you know, as a file
clerk at Columbia University. And I like
was running to the subway with reporters
chasing me. Um and it was just like the
the disjoint between the fact that I was
a cartoonist who appeared in the New
York Times and the fact that I was still
working full-time and not making any
money.
And so basically all of the stress of
being a big-time cartoonist without any
of the protection or any of the money.
That I really rough and basically you
just have to center yourself and just
you know, I mean you know how it is. You
just you
you can't go on, you must go on.
You know, I mean
>> Tell me about it.
>> There's no choice.
>> I had every I had every
network
in America in their giant vans with
their spotlights parked in front of my
house.
>> Yeah, that's
>> It was rough.
>> salacious
>> Yeah, it's salacious. Um
Yeah, they were buzzing at all hours of
the night, too.
Um
I never uh let's see. I never heard
about Blockbuster censoring until Ted. I
missed that. I was too young to know.
Yeah, um well, it's I wish I'd
forgotten.
Uh but yeah, I guess that'll happen
someday. Um
Pittsburgh says I I shouldn't even say
that Kasich is socially moderate. I
should say that he's totally moderate
compared to someone as rabid as Trump.
I think that's well said.
Um
Kasich was considered a right-wing nut
when he was in Congress.
>> Which is funny. He actually was
considered a right-wing nut when he was
in Congress.
>> Yeah, it was a tonal thing. It's like
how John John McCain was a rabid
right-winger, but he he had a calm
voice.
>> Yeah.
John McCain, I I disagree with John
McCain on 95% of the issues, but man,
nobody nobody on Capitol Hill was a
bigger supporter of mine than John
McCain.
>> That's amazing. Um
RAC wants to know if we have any updates
on Jamal Thomas. I'm afraid not. Last I
heard was um
you know, he was
recovering. You know, it's a process.
>> Let me see if I have his cell phone.
I must. I'm
>> I have it.
>> Okay, good.
>> Yeah, if you don't have it, I'll send it
to you. Um all right, John, we have a
few minutes left.
>> it.
>> So
Uh Victor Orban, PM of Hungary,
um vetoed any European country's leader
can veto uh any EU decision to celebrate
the fourth anniversary of the Russian
invasion of Ukraine. The [snorts] um the
the EU was going to lend a bunch of
money more to Ukraine. I mean, you know,
it's like not really that generous, but
lend it to them and also impose new
sanctions against Russia. I don't know
what new sanctions they found hiding up
between the sofa cushions, but they uh
and but Viktor Orbán is pissed because
the Ukrainians are accused in his mind
of disrupting this uh
this oil pipeline from Russia that goes
via Ukraine to Hungary and Slovakia. And
he's like, "You're cutting off our oil.
>> Yet another
>> the Ukies any more money."
>> Yeah, yet another winter.
>> Right?
>> Yeah, yet another winter. Um I'm
inclined to believe the Ukrainians are
guilty of what they're accused of here.
>> Agreed.
>> think?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm no fan of Orbán's, but I
think he's right.
>> And you know, and and so he's being
accused of I mean, the other thing is do
you really at this point want to throw
good money after bad? I mean
>> See, that's a good question.
I don't. Like as an American taxpayer,
I don't.
>> I mean, but whatever you think of the
cause, I mean, the Ukrainians are not
going to win this.
And it's also it was very funny to me.
Zelensky recently said, you know,
pointed out, "Well, Russia hasn't
achieved all their goals." And then
Russia's like,
"We have not achieved all our goals.
That's why it's still going on."
It was pretty funny. That's a really
characteristically Russian response.
>> Yeah.
It is. And you know, this is the thing,
too. It comes back to the the question
of like why why won't the Russians
settle this? Because they're winning.
There's no reason to settle this.
They're winning.
>> Um hey, this is a good This is a good
suggestion, Flanderina. Have you guys
considered setting up a way we can
submit questions before the show?
>> Oh, that's a good question.
>> Well, there is a way.
>> Oh, is there?
>> Yeah, I mean, we have an email address.
We could just say uh
>> didn't even know we had an email
address.
>> We do. Um so, uh let me see if I can if
I can So, we could uh
I'm but but let me talk to Robbie and
find out what the best way to do this
is. Maybe cuz we need a way for them to
be handleable and sort of arrangeable in
a way for Robbie to be able to put them
up.
>> Cuz currently, Robbie filters them
through and posts them and then we watch
them in real time, but he sorts through
so we don't have to read all the
non-question comments.
>> Right.
>> And um and so, but if when Robbie's not
available like to as today, there's no
way to do that. But, that's a great
idea. Um we could I mean, we could just
set up an a question inbox and um I
mean, I The thing is, I don't want to
open zillions of emails. So, I'm
wondering
what the best logistical way to do that
is. Um
I don't know. I guess maybe you could
just put the question in the subject
line, right? Then you could just see it
you see it all as a list. That's
probably the way.
>> Yeah.
>> Or we could set up a we could set up a a
uh
well, yeah, a WhatsApp or something like
that.
>> Teddy,
>> It's a good idea.
>> We only have about a minute or a minute
and a half left. I've got to ask you as
a New Yorker,
>> Mhm.
>> what do we make of this giant
snowball fight yesterday?
>> Oh, good. I'm glad you brought that up.
So, so Washington Square Park uh in
Greenwich Village is uh you know,
basically has always been kind of like
the center of counterculture fun in New
York. It's where the Halloween parade
ends up for in a big party. Um it's uh
it's in the summer, it's kind of
raucous. You're always able to buy drugs
there. Um so, and there's always like
street performances and stuff. So,
anyway, uh a spontaneous snowball fight
broke up broke out between young people,
mostly boys,
in in the park. Someone dropped a dime
on the snowball fight and called 911.
>> Because that's what you do when somebody
is going to throw snow.
>> Right. These are obviously Well, this
reminds me of the time in the early '80s
when I had first moved to New York and
uh there were police helicopters over my
apartment. Learn literally there was a
raccoon in the street and the NYPD had
been dispatched to do something about
it. I'm like, there's nothing to do. It
is a raccoon.
>> [laughter]
>> There's just ignore it. But anyway, um
yeah, so they called they called the
cops. The cops came and then the kids
started were started throwing snowballs
at the cops. The cops are acting like it
was a 9/11 terrorist act um and the
police unions are winging and they're
pressuring the mayor. The mayor had a
pretty good response. Um this is a this
is right-wing Um you know, the
cops shouldn't have responded at all. Um
to the extent that I have any sympathy
here for the police, it was very wet icy
snow and it was like probably not a lot
of fun to catch a big wet icy snowball
at the back of the head and I think a
couple of cops claimed to have been
mildly injured. So, that kind of sucks.
The cops shouldn't have been there in
the first place though is my take.
What's yours?
>> Yeah, the cops shouldn't have been there
in the first place, but the New York
Post should be ashamed of itself for
making it this Mumdani versus the cops,
you know, riot.
>> Ridiculous.
>> what it was. It was a snowball fight.
>> And I like what Mumdani said. He said,
you know, leave the cops alone. If you
want to throw a snowball at someone,
throw it at me.
>> There you go.
>> All right. Anyway, all right, thanks
John. We will see you back. We're here
Monday through Friday 9:00 a.m. and then
which means we'll be back tomorrow
Thursday at 9:00 a.m. Eastern time.
Thanks for watching. Please stay tuned
for a TMI show with me and Mele Chan
coming up right now. Bye. Bye,
everybody.
>> [music]
[music]